Commencement Programs UP037
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Commencement Programs
1857 -- 2022
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Commencement Office
UP037
4.15 Linear Feet
148 Digital Object(s)
0.98 Gigabytes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series: Commencement programs; Doctoral hooding ceremony; and Graduate School Commencement programs.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the commencement programs for Tufts College and later Tufts University and its schools which record all degree recipients including honorary and featured speakers. It includes commencement programs for undergraduate and graduate degrees beginning in 1857.
- Combined Commencement programs, 1857 -- 2021; UP037.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 148 Digital Object(s); 0.98 Gigabytes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains commencement programs for Tufts College and later Tufts University and its schools. They record all degree recipients including honorary and featured speakers. The bulk of these programs include all schools bound in one volume.
  Arrangement
  This collection is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Commencement Programs, 1857 -- 1900; UP037.001.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 19.7 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1901 -- 1910; UP037.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Forty-fifth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1901-06-18; UP037.001.001.00002.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Forty-sixth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1902-06-18; UP037.001.001.00002.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Forty-seventh Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1903-06-17; UP037.001.001.00002.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Forty-eighth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1904-06-15; UP037.001.001.00002.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Forty-ninth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1905-06-20; UP037.001.001.00002.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Fiftieth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1906-06-20; UP037.001.001.00002.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Fifty-first Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1907-06-19; UP037.001.001.00002.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Fifty-second Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1908-06-17; UP037.001.001.00002.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Fifty-third Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1909-06-16; UP037.001.001.00002.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Fifty-fourth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1910-06-15; UP037.001.001.00002.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1911 -- 1920; UP037.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Fifty-fifth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1911-06-21; UP037.001.001.00003.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Fifty-sixth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1912-06-19; UP037.001.001.00003.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Fifty-seventh Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1913-06-18; UP037.001.001.00003.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Fifty-eighth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1914-06-17; UP037.001.001.00003.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Fifty-ninth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1915-06-16; UP037.001.001.00003.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Sixtieth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1916-06-21; UP037.001.001.00003.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Sixty-first Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1917-06-18; UP037.001.001.00003.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Sixty-second Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1918-06-17; UP037.001.001.00003.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Sixty-third Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1919-06-23; UP037.001.001.00003.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Sixty-fourth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1920-06-21; UP037.001.001.00003.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1921 -- 1930; UP037.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Sixty-fifth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1921-06-20; UP037.001.001.00004.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Sixty-sixth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1922-06-19; UP037.001.001.00004.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Sixty-seventh Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1923-06-18; UP037.001.001.00004.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Sixty-eighth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1924-06-16; UP037.001.001.00004.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Sixty-ninth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1925-06-15; UP037.001.001.00004.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventieth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1926-06-14; UP037.001.001.00004.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-first Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1927-06-20; UP037.001.001.00004.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-second Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1928-06-18; UP037.001.001.00004.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-third Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1929-06-17; UP037.001.001.00004.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-third Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1929-06-17; UP037.001.001.00004.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-fourth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1930-06-16; UP037.001.001.00004.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-fourth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1930-06-16; UP037.001.001.00004.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-fourth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1930-06-16; UP037.001.001.00004.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1931 -- 1940; UP037.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - Seventy-fifth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1931-06-15; UP037.001.001.00005.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-fifth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1931-06-15; UP037.001.001.00005.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-sixth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1932-06-13; UP037.001.001.00005.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-sixth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1932-06-13; UP037.001.001.00005.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-sixth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1932-06-13; UP037.001.001.00005.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-seventh Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1933-06-19; UP037.001.001.00005.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-seventh Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1933-06-19; UP037.001.001.00005.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-eighth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1934-06-18; UP037.001.001.00005.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-eighth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1934-06-18; UP037.001.001.00005.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Program for Commencement, 1935; UP037.001.001.00005.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Seventy-ninth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1935-06-17; UP037.001.001.00005.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eightieth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1936-06-15; UP037.001.001.00005.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-first Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1937-06-14; UP037.001.001.00005.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-second Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1938-06-13; UP037.001.001.00005.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-third Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1939-06-19; UP037.001.001.00005.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-third Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1939-06-19; UP037.001.001.00005.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-fourth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1940-06-17; UP037.001.001.00005.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-fourth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1940-06-17; UP037.001.001.00005.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1941 -- 1950; UP037.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Eighty-fifth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1941-06-15; UP037.001.001.00006.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-sixth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1942-05-17; UP037.001.001.00006.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-sixth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1942-05-17; UP037.001.001.00006.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1943-01-26; UP037.001.001.00006.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1943-03-28; UP037.001.001.00006.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-seventh Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1943-05-16; UP037.001.001.00006.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1943-10-17; UP037.001.001.00006.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1943-12-30; UP037.001.001.00006.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1944-02-13; UP037.001.001.00006.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-eighth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1944-06-18; UP037.001.001.00006.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-eighth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1944-06-18; UP037.001.001.00006.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1944-09-24; UP037.001.001.00006.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1944-09-24; UP037.001.001.00006.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1944-10-22; UP037.001.001.00006.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1945-02-18; UP037.001.001.00006.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Eighty-ninth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1945-06-17; UP037.001.001.00006.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1945-10-21; UP037.001.001.00006.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1946-02-24; UP037.001.001.00006.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1946-03-31; UP037.001.001.00006.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Ninetieth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1946-06-16; UP037.001.001.00006.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1947-02-09; UP037.001.001.00006.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Ninety-first Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1947-06-15; UP037.001.001.00006.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts College Degree Convocation, 1948-02-15; UP037.001.001.00006.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Ninety-second Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1948-06-20; UP037.001.001.00006.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Ninety-third Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1949-06-19; UP037.001.001.00006.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Ninety-fourth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1950-06-11; UP037.001.001.00006.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1951 -- 1960; UP037.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - Ninety-fifth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1951-06-10; UP037.001.001.00007.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Ninety-sixth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1952-06-08; UP037.001.001.00007.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Ninety-seventh Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1953-06-14; UP037.001.001.00007.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Ninety-eighth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1954-06-13; UP037.001.001.00007.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Ninety-ninth Annual Commencement of Tufts College, 1955-06-12; UP037.001.001.00007.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - One Hundredth Commencement Tufts University, 1956-06-10; UP037.001.001.00007.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - One Hundred and First Annual Commencement of Tufts University, 1957-06-09; UP037.001.001.00007.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - One Hundred and Second Annual Commencement of Tufts University, 1958-06-08; UP037.001.001.00007.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The One Hundred and Third Annual Commencement of Tufts University, 1959-06-07; UP037.001.001.00007.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The One Hundred and Fourth Annual Commencement of Tufts University, 1960-06-12; UP037.001.001.00007.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Commencement Program, 1960; UP037.001.001.00007.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1961 -- 1965; UP037.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - The 105th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1961-06-11; UP037.001.001.00008.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 106th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1962-06-10; UP037.001.001.00008.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 107th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1963-06-09; UP037.001.001.00008.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 108th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1964-06-07; UP037.001.001.00008.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 109th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1965-06-06; UP037.001.001.00008.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1966 -- 1970; UP037.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    - The 110th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1966-06-05; UP037.001.001.00009.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 111th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1967-06-04; UP037.001.001.00009.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 112th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1968-06-09; UP037.001.001.00009.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 113th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1969-06-01; UP037.001.001.00009.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - University Convocation, 1970-05-30; UP037.001.001.00009.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 0 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 114th Annual Commencement Tufts University, N/A; UP037.001.001.00009.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 114th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1970-05-31; UP037.001.001.00009.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1971 -- 1975; UP037.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - The 115th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1971-06-06; UP037.001.001.00010.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 116th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1972-06-04; UP037.001.001.00010.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - The 117th Annual Commencement Tufts University, 1973-06-03; UP037.001.001.00010.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 118th Commencement Exercises, 1974-06-15; UP037.001.001.00010.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 119th Commencement Exercises, 1975-05-25; UP037.001.001.00010.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1976 -- 1980; UP037.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 120th Commencement Exercises, 1976-05-23; UP037.001.001.00011.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 121st Commencement Exercises, 1977-05-22; UP037.001.001.00011.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 121st Commencement Exercises, 1977-05-22; UP037.001.001.00011.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 122nd Commencement Exercises, 1978-05-21; UP037.001.001.00011.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 124th Commencement Exercises, 1980-05-25; UP037.001.001.00011.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1981 -- 1985; UP037.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 125th Commencement Exercises, 1981-05-31; UP037.001.001.00012.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 126th Commencement Exercises, 1982-05-30; UP037.001.001.00012.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 127th Commencement Exercises, 1983-05-29; UP037.001.001.00012.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 128th Commencement Exercises, 1984-05-20; UP037.001.001.00012.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 129th Commencement Exercises, 1985-05-19; UP037.001.001.00012.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1986 -- 1988; UP037.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 130th Commencement Exercises, 1986-05-18; UP037.001.001.00013.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 131st Commencement Exercises, 1987-05-17; UP037.001.001.00013.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 132nd Commencement Exercises, 1988-05-22; UP037.001.001.00013.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1989 -- 1991; UP037.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 133rd Commencement Exercises, 1989-05-21; UP037.001.001.00014.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 134th Commencement Exercises, 1990-05-20; UP037.001.001.00014.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 135th Commencement Exercises, 1991-05-12; UP037.001.001.00014.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1992 -- 1994; UP037.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 136th Commencement Exercises, 1992-05-17; UP037.001.001.00015.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 137th Commencement Exercises, 1993-05-23; UP037.001.001.00015.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 138th Commencement Exercises, 1994-05-22; UP037.001.001.00015.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1995 -- 1996; UP037.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 139th Commencement Exercises, 1995-05-21; UP037.001.001.00016.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 140th Commencement Exercises, 1996-05-19; UP037.001.001.00016.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1997 -- 1998; UP037.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 141st Commencement Exercises, 1997-05-18; UP037.001.001.00017.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 142nd Commencement Exercises, 1998-05-17; UP037.001.001.00017.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1999 -- 2000; UP037.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 143rd Commencement Exercises, 1999-05-23; UP037.001.001.00018.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 1)
    - Tufts University 144th Commencement Exercises, 2000-05-21; UP037.001.001.00018.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 2001; UP037.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    - Commencement, 2001-05-20; UP037.001.002.00001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 0 Megabytes (Box 2)
    - 145th Commencement Exercises, 2001-05-20; UP037.001.002.00001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Commencement Programs, 2002; UP037.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
    - 146th Commencement Exercises, 2002-05-19; UP037.001.002.00002.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.44 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Commencement Programs, 2003; UP037.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    - Commencement, 2003-05-18; UP037.001.002.00003.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2)
    - 147th Commencement Exercises, 2003-05-18; UP037.001.002.00003.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Commencement Programs, 2004; UP037.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    - 148th Commencement Exercises, 2004-05-23; UP037.001.002.00004.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 149th Commencement Exercises, 2005-05-22; UP037.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    - 149th Commencement Exercises, 2005-05-22; UP037.001.002.00005.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 150th Commencement Exercises, 2006-05-21; UP037.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
    - 150th Commencement, 2006-05-21; UP037.001.002.00006.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 151th Commencement Exercises, 2007-05-20; UP037.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
    - Commencement 2007, 2007-05-20; UP037.001.002.00007.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 152th Commencement Exercises, 2008-05-18; UP037.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
    Also includes a program specific to the School of Arts and Sciences and the School of Engineering.
    - Commencement 2008, 2008-05-18; UP037.001.002.00008.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2)
    - 152nd Commencement, 2008-05-18; UP037.001.002.00008.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 153th Commencement Exercises, 2009-05-17; UP037.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
    Joint program that includes: School of Arts and Sciences, School of Engineering, School of Medicine and Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, School of Dental Medicine, The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine, and the Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy.
    - Commencement 2009, 2009-05-17; UP037.001.002.00009.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 154th Commencement Exercises, 2010-05-23; UP037.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
    Joint program that includes: School of Arts and Sciences, School of Engineering, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, School of Medicine and Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, School of Dental Medicine, The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine, Public Health and Professional Degree Programs, and the Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy.
    - Commencement 2010, 2010-05-23; UP037.001.002.00010.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 45 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 155th Commencement Exercises, 2011-05-22; UP037.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
    - Commencement 2011, 2011-05-22; UP037.001.002.00011.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 48 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 156th Commencement Exercises, 2012-05-20; UP037.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
    - Commencement 2012, 2012-05-20; UP037.001.002.00012.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 49 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 157th Commencement, 2013-05-19; UP037.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
    - Commencement 2013, UP037.001.002.00013.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 51 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 158th Commencement, 2014-05-18; UP037.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    - Commencement 2014, UP037.001.002.00014.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - 159th Commencement, 2015-05-17; UP037.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Commencement programs, 2016-05-22; UP037.001.002.00016 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 161st Commencement, 2017-05-21; UP037.001.002.00017; .1 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 162nd Commencement, 2018 May 20; UP037.000104 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 163rd Commencement, 2019 May 19; UP037.000105 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 164th Commencement, 2020 May 17; UP037.000106 (Box 2, Folder 20)